<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://gpsoftcc.github.io</id>
    <title>Must.cheng</title>
    <updated>2019-09-25T07:31:37.611Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://gpsoftcc.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://gpsoftcc.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>foo fighters</subtitle>
    <logo>https://gpsoftcc.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://gpsoftcc.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2019, Must.cheng</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[25th,September]]></title>
        <id>https://gpsoftcc.github.io/post/25thseptember</id>
        <link href="https://gpsoftcc.github.io/post/25thseptember">
        </link>
        <updated>2019-09-25T07:06:39.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>How time flies!<br>
I sometimes feel that time flies very quickly. Three or four hours passed in a flash.<br>
The weather in SZ in fine. It is a little cooler than the past few days. My daily life is the same as before, there is no change, all is reading and work and so on.<br>
I have made a decision to lose weight but  I am as fat as before. I am not eating less but I eat less healthy food and eat more junk food. So the decision to lose weight is not a wise one.<br>
I am trying to form a good habit of learning, such as reading books, learning to practice listening skill and so on. I hope I can keep the good habit of learning.<br>
I confused about my carrer path but now I have decided what to do. I will move to another city in a few days.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The first diary in English]]></title>
        <id>https://gpsoftcc.github.io/post/the-first-diary-in-english</id>
        <link href="https://gpsoftcc.github.io/post/the-first-diary-in-english">
        </link>
        <updated>2019-09-20T08:24:48.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I think I should write a diary in English every day because it can help me to improve my English writing skills. In the beginning, there will be a lot of mistakes. But I believe that my English writing skills will be improved if I insist on do it.<br>
Now, I understand one thing through many years of exam--- If your mother language writing skills are not really good, maybe your English writing skills are not good too, because if you don't know how to write a good article in your native language, you also don't know how to write a good article in English. I think it is easy to understand.<br>
In recent days, I study English most of the time and I always feel time flies. It is a really good thing. Because if you feel time flies you must like the things which you are doing now.<br>
Wow, although this diary is written very terrible, it cost me a lot of time. It is time to go to work.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[懒惰与焦虑]]></title>
        <id>https://gpsoftcc.github.io/post/test</id>
        <link href="https://gpsoftcc.github.io/post/test">
        </link>
        <updated>2019-08-18T01:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>感觉自己时长处于一种焦虑之中，觉得自己不够努力，还有很多事情要去做，但是因为自己的懒惰与好玩，事情并未如愿完成，然后再进入新一轮的焦虑之中。<br>
今天该背的单词还没有背，该复习的题还没有刷，该备的课还没有备......<br>
我感觉还是压力不够吧，有压力才有动力，虽然压力下挺累。</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>